There's no doubt that I have a sweet tooth – I crave cakes and biscuits and could happily finish off a bar of chocolate in minutes.
毫无疑问，我是个爱吃甜食的人——我渴望吃蛋糕和饼干，还能在几分钟内开心地吃完一块巧克力。
I'm sure I'm not alone, the sweet sugary taste is addictive but the big question is, is it bad for me?
我确信不止我一个人这样，甜甜的味道让人上瘾，但关键问题是，它对我有害吗？
I think I know the answer!
我想我知道答案！
Sugar is everywhere.
糖无处不在。
Even if sweet stuff isn't your thing it's hard to avoid.
即使你不喜欢甜食，也很难避免。
In the UK, we consume over two million tonnes of sugar every year but often we don’t know we’re eating it.
在英国，我们每年消耗超过两百万吨糖，但我们常常意识不到自己在吃糖。
There have been many health campaigns, telling us about the dangers of consuming too much sugar and we have probably learnt that it should be eaten in moderation but we may be unaware of the added sugar we consume that's found in the food and drink we think of as healthy or savoury, such as low-fat yoghurt and sauces.
许多健康运动都在告诉我们摄入过多糖的危害，我们可能已经知道应该适度食用，但我们可能不知道在我们认为健康或可口的食品和饮料中也含有添加糖，比如低脂酸奶和调味酱。
The obvious negative effect of eating sugar is on our dental health – tooth decay is a big problem in children, partly caused by drinking too many sugary drinks.
吃糖的一个明显负面影响是对我们牙齿健康的损害——蛀牙是儿童的一个大问题，部分原因是饮用了太多含糖饮料。
Public Health England claims a child in England has a tooth removed in hospital every 10 minutes due to preventable decay.
英国公共卫生部门称，在英格兰，每10分钟就有一名儿童因为可预防的蛀牙在医院拔牙。
But even if you can escape the dentist's drill, there are more worrying negative effects - repeatedly eating too much sugar can lead to weight gain and even obesity, leading to an increased risk of diabetes, heart disease and liver disease.
但即使你能避开牙医的钻头，还有更令人担忧的负面影响——反复摄入过多糖会导致体重增加，甚至肥胖，进而增加患糖尿病、心脏病和肝病的风险。
So what can we do to cut down on our sugar intake?
那么，我们能做些什么来减少糖的摄入量呢？
Well, there are low-sugar recipes you can try and apparently there are alternative foods to help us beat the sweet cravings.
嗯，你可以尝试一些低糖食谱，而且显然有替代食品可以帮助我们抑制对甜食的渴望。
But potentially the most effective method is to tax the sugar we consume.
但很可能最有效的方法是对我们消费的糖征税。
It's what several countries have been doing for a while and the UK has recently jumped on the bandwagon, by forcing manufacturers to pay a levy on the high-sugar drinks they sell.
这已经是几个国家一段时间以来的做法了，英国最近也紧跟潮流，迫使制造商对他们销售的高糖饮料缴纳税款。
It's up to the manufacturers if they pass the cost on to consumers.
是否将成本转嫁给消费者取决于制造商。
But will it work?
但这会有效吗？
University of Bedfordshire nutrition expert Dr Daniel Bailey told BBC Online that: "The increase in tax placed on soft drinks will make products more expensive, but will this actually discourage people from buying them?"
贝德福德大学营养专家丹尼尔・贝利博士告诉BBC在线：“对软饮料加税会使产品更贵，但这真的会阻止人们购买吗？”
Maybe if you're addicted to the stuff, you'd accept paying more to buy it.
如果你对这种东西上瘾，你可能会接受花更多钱购买。
But in the UK at least, several soft drinks companies have already reduced the sugar content of their products to avoid the tax.
但至少在英国，几家软饮料公司已经降低了产品的糖含量以避免缴税。
Obviously it's better to do something rather than nothing to help improve the well-being of everyone.
显然，做点什么总比什么都不做好，这有助于改善每个人的健康。
But with so many temptations out there, I'm not sure how easy it will be to cure my sweet tooth.
但外面有这么多诱惑，我不确定要改掉爱吃甜食的习惯有多容易。